[
  {
    "question": "Your friends have never heard of Design Thinking. They are intrigued and want to know more about it. Which of the following is the best definition of Design Thinking as used in our course?",
    "answers": [
      "Systematic, replicable approach to the creative process and to new, innovative solutions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Our Design Thinking approach uses a series of four questions. Select the correct series.",
    "answers": ["What Is, What If, What Wows, What Works"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are eager to become more innovative. Which of the following is the best way to begin your path to successful innovation?",
    "answers": ["Assess the current reality."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes essentials of our problem-solving approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Human-centered, possibility-driven, option-focused, and iterative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Our story of The Good Kitchen provides a real-world example of which of the following statements?",
    "answers": [
      "Reframing the original problem can uncover larger, better opportunities."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have been asked to conduct ethnographic research with a new audience. You are excited to discover unarticulated needs! Based on our Design Thinking approach, which of the following tools should you use first?",
    "answers": ["Journey map"]
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Design Thinking process, The Good Kitchen design team enlisted a broad group of stakeholders and used a variety of co-creation tools. Why?",
    "answers": ["Create ownership and engagement, and produce better ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering whether a problem is wicked or tame is one way to identify a problem, challenge, or opportunity that could benefit from a Design Thinking approach. Which of the following is a typical characteristic of wicked problems?",
    "answers": ["Complex, fluid situation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You started using a Design Thinking approach and – partway through – you realized that your original problem definition needs to change! What does this indicate?",
    "answers": [
      "This is normal. You have learned more about the context of the problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to apply what you’ve learned to this point in our course! You review potential opportunities in your organization (work, school, community). Which of the following qualities is most suitable to practicing newly developing Design Thinking skills?",
    "answers": [
      "Start with a project that is human-centered. The ability to gain a deep understanding of the actual people involved is possible and important."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Eric Folger’s example, the organization was not yet familiar with Design Thinking. What was one way that Eric introduced Design Thinking into the project?",
    "answers": ["Explored the issues driving customer decision-making"]
  },
  {
    "question": "During Eric’s initial research, he and his colleague talked with people in their homes. Which of the following did Eric most want to learn from these people?",
    "answers": ["What motivated them in life"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Eric Folger, which of the following is a recommended way to manage internal anxiety at the beginning of the Design Thinking process?",
    "answers": [
      "Trust your ability to explore, even when it feels uncomfortable."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eric Folger’s graphic demonstrates a fundamental characteristic of the Design Thinking process. Which of the following best expresses that characteristic?",
    "answers": [
      "The greatest anxiety typically appears right before the solution comes together."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have discovered a good opportunity for Design Thinking! Which of the following is most appropriate to framing the scope for a Design Thinking project?",
    "answers": [
      "Explore the project from broader and narrower perspectives to examine different angles."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on our Design Thinking approach, which of the following best describes “scope”?",
    "answers": [
      "A choice, depending on a variety of factors and with no single right answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is recommended when framing the scope of a Design Thinking challenge?",
    "answers": [
      "Treat the scope like a hypothesis and be ready to adjust the definition as needed throughout the process."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to our Design Thinking approach, which of the following best describes a design brief?",
    "answers": [
      "A concise summary of the current state of your thinking about your project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is most consistent with our approach to planning a Design Thinking project?",
    "answers": [
      "Even though our environment is full of uncertainty, the management of our project needn’t be."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Clay Maxwell’s healthcare example, the Design Thinking team zoomed in to focus on which of the following?",
    "answers": ["People"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In our Design Thinking approach, which planning component looks at the specific tools you will use as you work through the four questions?",
    "answers": ["Research plan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As you develop your people plan, which of the following is the most important group to consider?",
    "answers": [
      "The entire range of people your project might have an impact on, as well as stakeholders and the core project team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are discussing your research plan with a friend. The friend asks about the role of secondary data in Design Thinking. Based on our approach, which of these is your best reply?",
    "answers": [
      "Secondary data can be useful to avoid repeating existing solutions, but the heart of the research will involve gathering primary data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have started to conduct interviews. It was all going so well – and, suddenly, you feel stuck and scared! Which of the following is a recommended technique?",
    "answers": [
      "Revisit your people plan. Consider how other people in your network can help you get unstuck."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As you do your research, you are taking careful notes. Which of the following is also a recommended practice during research?",
    "answers": ["Consider how you will share what you are learning."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is demonstrated in Ryan Jacoby’s stories of ethnographic interviews?",
    "answers": [
      "What people believe they are doing and what they actually do may be two different things."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have been asked to conduct research on an existing product. You are allowed to interview one group of people. Applying our Design Thinking approach, which of these groups is likely to be your best source for interesting insights?",
    "answers": [
      "People who don’t use the product at all and can’t imagine they ever would"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In our Design Thinking approach, we recommend advance preparation before ethnographic interviews. During the actual interviews, which of the following recommendations is most likely to provide helpful insights?",
    "answers": [
      "Follow the energy to allow an open, active conversation and new lines of questioning in each interview."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have been invited to provide feedback on a colleague’s Design Thinking project. Which of the following is your most helpful approach?",
    "answers": ["Beginner’s mind"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best summarizes the advice offered by Dawan Stanford in his video?",
    "answers": [
      "The project will become ambiguous. Hold on through that ride. The process, when you trust it, gives you something more."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a fundamental requirement for finding innovation opportunities?",
    "answers": ["A prepared mind"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these best describes a “natural law” governing the physics of growth and innovation as discussed in our course?",
    "answers": ["The only certainty is uncertainty."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your organization wants to be more innovative! As an organization starts looking for innovative solutions, which of the following recommendations is most likely to support success?",
    "answers": [
      "Start small and avoid dismissing opportunities before their potential can be assessed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your organization wants to overcome “growth gridlock” and the physics of stability. Which of the following is a recommended method to increase opportunities for the physics of innovation?",
    "answers": [
      "Look for areas where the future may diverge from the past, even if this involves areas of uncertainty."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to our research, what are three essential factors that characterize a prepared mind?",
    "answers": ["Learning mindset, broad repertoire, customer empathy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At its best, organizational innovation is primarily about creating which of the following?",
    "answers": ["Value"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these mindsets is most likely to lead to successful innovation?",
    "answers": ["Focus on advancement, growth and accomplishment."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are helping your company grow! Which of the following should be “front and center” as you move forward to innovate?",
    "answers": ["Customer problems"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your friend is interested in becoming more innovative at work and has asked for your help. Which piece of advice is most likely to help this new innovator?",
    "answers": [
      "Consider working with a structure and a process. It sounds paradoxical but it’s true."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are excited to expand your own mind for innovation. Which of the following is the best way to accomplish this?",
    "answers": [
      "Look for patterns and interconnections between seemingly disparate elements. Build on them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The MeYouHealth story focuses on a challenge: Engaging people in doing something about their own well-being. When Chris Cartter first encountered the challenge, what was his initial feeling?",
    "answers": [
      "It was a big question – and an area of opportunity he wanted to explore."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine that – similar to the MeYouHealth team – you are using an ethnographic approach to answer the “What Is” question. Which of the following interview strategies would you recommend to your team?",
    "answers": [
      "Go deep with a small number of interviews, rather than wide with a large number."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to learn even more about your interview subjects. Which of the following are examples of projective tools and approaches that you might use?",
    "answers": ["Journals, collages and pinwheels"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are working with a team on a Design Thinking project. During the “What Is” question, you begin to see patterns and themes emerging from your interviews. Exciting! Which of the following tools would you recommend to the team, to facilitate the search for patterns and themes and to capture systematic differences?",
    "answers": ["Mind mapping and personas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your design team is ready to generate some ideas! Using your knowledge of Design Thinking, which of the following approaches would you recommend?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask trigger questions. Allow individuals time for idea writing. Share results. Repeat."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "For Design Thinking teams, which of these is often the most difficult part of the entire design process?",
    "answers": ["Identifying insights"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a primary goal of the Identifying Insights step?",
    "answers": ["Establish design criteria."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the purpose of the gallery walk?",
    "answers": [
      "Create a structured approach to converge on a key set of design insights."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has just completed a gallery walk. The team has organized the many sticky notes into clusters. What is the team’s next best task?",
    "answers": ["Draw an insight out of each cluster."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has asked you to define “design criteria.” Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": ["A concise expression of the ideal end-state of our project"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the Design Thinking step of brainstorming?",
    "answers": [
      "A disciplined, repeatable process to help create many possible alternatives"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are leading a Design Thinking team. The team has identified a good opportunity for Design Thinking, framed an initial project scope, and drafted a design brief. As you look ahead, which of these is the first, best time for you to conduct a brainstorming session?",
    "answers": ["At the beginning of the “What If” stage"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To establish a successful brainstorming session, Rachel Brozenske recommends considering three aspects. What are they?",
    "answers": ["Environment, session, action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "During the brainstorming session, Rachel Brozenske recommends setting a tone that enables participants to focus on “ideas” rather than “qualities.” Your team asks you to explain the difference. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": ["An idea makes a quality actionable."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are facilitating a brainstorming session. Which of the following tools are your best choice to help participants generate ideas?",
    "answers": ["Trigger questions and analogies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team member has asked you to explain the difference between brainstorming and concept development. Which of these is your best explanation?",
    "answers": [
      "Concept development takes individual ideas generated during brainstorming and combines them into powerful bundles for evaluating against our criteria."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After a brainstorming session, we want to take action by doing two things. What are they?",
    "answers": ["Organize and combine"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best guidance for conducting an effective Design Thinking brainstorming session?",
    "answers": ["There’s no risk in writing down a bad idea."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to assist your team by providing a Design Thinking tool during concept development. Which of these is your best choice?",
    "answers": ["Chili table"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have just completed a brainstorming session. During the session, your wonderful team generated – literally – hundreds of ideas! What is your next, best step?",
    "answers": ["Move quickly from brainstorming into concept development."]
  },
  {
    "question": "A friend asks you to explain the purpose of the Design Thinking napkin pitch. Which of the following is your best reply?",
    "answers": [
      "A simple, consistent format for summarizing and communicating our concepts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of using napkin pitches in Design Thinking?",
    "answers": ["Explore multiple options and let other people validate them."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Design Thinking “wow zone” is at the intersection of three “wow” measurements. What are they?",
    "answers": ["Customer, execution, business-model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In our case study of IBM trade shows, the George P. Johnson (GPJ) design team began by stepping away from existing models of trade shows. Which of the following Design Thinking techniques does the team’s action demonstrate?",
    "answers": ["Reframing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is ready to tackle step 11: Surface key assumptions. A team member asks you why this step is important. Which of the following is your best reply?",
    "answers": [
      "This step enables us to gather data about why our assumptions may or may not be true."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is ready to begin testing key assumptions. Which of the following techniques is the fastest, lowest-cost, lowest-risk way to test an assumption when you already have the necessary data?",
    "answers": ["Thought experiment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have worked with your team to brainstorm ideas, develop concepts, create napkin pitches and surface key assumptions. Great work! You are ready to introduce assumption testing. What is the purpose of assumption testing?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify the “make-or-break” (absolute success or failure) elements of our concepts."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your design team is still in the early stages of innovation – and they are ready to test assumptions. You have explained that assumption testing includes four key tests. Of the four key tests, which two are generally the most important to test first?",
    "answers": ["Value and execution"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a best practice for conducting thought experiments?",
    "answers": ["Take a hypothesis-driven approach."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team wants to test an assumption, but past data sources do not provide sufficient help. Which of the following is the best, lowest-risk way to test assumptions when you need more than the existing, published data?",
    "answers": ["Field experiment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A friend asks you to explain the goal of a Design Thinking learning launch. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": ["Test remaining critical assumptions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your design team have created prototypes, run co-creation sessions with stakeholders, and incorporated feedback into your prototype. Now you want to test your concept with a wider audience. You are ready to design a learning launch. Which of the following is essential to a successful learning launch?",
    "answers": ["Make the experience feel genuine."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is preparing for its first learning launch. Which of the following is a desired outcome of a first learning launch?",
    "answers": [
      "A set of metrics that will allow us to go back and improve the solution we’ve created"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Tim Ogilvie’s explanation of in-market experiments, he talks about shifting our focus to key assumptions. Which of the following is the most accurate statement throughout that shift?",
    "answers": ["User needs are still here."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tim Ogilvie discusses similarities between conducting in-market experimentation and launching a start-up business. During in-market experimentation, which of the following is the most important assumption to test?",
    "answers": ["Our customers want it."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the most effective use of the thought experiments layer (row) in a learning plan timeline?",
    "answers": [
      "Revisit the thought experiments layer throughout the timeline."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team wants to conduct a 4D (four-dimensional), live, in-market experiment. Which of the following is your best choice for the prototype?",
    "answers": ["Lemonade stand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is creating the prototype for a 4D (four-dimensional), live, in-market experiment. Which of the following is a recommended characteristic of the prototype?",
    "answers": [
      "Polished and finished to encourage users to believe it is the real thing (even though parts of it are still fake)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tim Ogilvie discusses validity-oriented thinking, based on concepts introduced by Roger Martin. Which of the following is a characteristic of validity thinking?",
    "answers": ["Possibility oriented"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your design team have been working through the Design Thinking process, developing what may be an innovative product! The team is ready to perform an in-market experiment. A team member asks you for guidance about the relationship between the in-market experiment and metrics. Which of the following is your best guidance?",
    "answers": [
      "We may fail on hitting the metric targets, but we must not fail on the learning."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to test your value-creation assumptions. Which of the following is a recommended technique to help users “pre-experience” your concept?",
    "answers": ["Prototype"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is getting ready to create early prototypes. They ask you to explain a “good prototype.” Which of the following is your best guidance?",
    "answers": [
      "It always tells a story that invites other people into the experience with you."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has decided to take Dave Bishop’s recommendation and use a “continuum of prototyping.” Which of the following is a key advantage of this approach?",
    "answers": [
      "The continuum offers a high return on investment throughout the prototyping process."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have been asked to prototype a user interface consisting of 50-100 screens. You are testing for usability. Which of the following is your best choice?",
    "answers": [
      "Learn more about the users so that you can focus the prototype on the screens the user is most likely to care about."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are conducting an early usability test for a new medical kiosk. Your goals are to make the kiosk easier to use and more inviting. Which of the following is a best practice for your first prototype?",
    "answers": [
      "The interaction can be created with simple materials, such as paper and pen."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are sharing your prototype with a potential customer. The person is providing feedback! What is your best response?",
    "answers": ["Listen to the feedback. Ask clarifying questions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are conducting an early prototyping session with a stakeholder. The stakeholder says, “Well, I see this part and this part – but how would the next thing happen?” Which of the following is your strongest reply?",
    "answers": ["What makes sense to you?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are preparing to conduct a co-creation session with a stakeholder. Your shared goal is to improve the customer experience. Which is your best choice to bring with you to the meeting?",
    "answers": ["One poster"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to learn more about which potential features of your solution might appeal to a specific group of users. You plan to meet with one target user. Which of the following is a recommended co-creation technique?",
    "answers": ["Card sort"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team wants to know what potential users are feeling and to obtain quick feedback on your new concept. Which of these is your best method?",
    "answers": ["Co-creation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your colleagues are actively seeking ways to improve the new-hire experience at your organization. Your team has been working through the steps of the Design Thinking process. Earlier today, you conducted an initial learning launch. Overall, the results of the learning launch looked promising! What is your next, best step?",
    "answers": ["Iterate based on the results and revisit steps as needed."]
  },
  {
    "question": "When considering the overall risk/investment relationship in a Design Thinking project, which of the following would you test for first?",
    "answers": ["Need"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Joshua Marcuse introduced the importance/difficulty matrix as a method for prioritizing ideas and determining which ideas to focus on. Which of the following is a suggested best practice when using the matrix?",
    "answers": [
      "Build a portfolio of ideas. Ask yourself, “What are things I could do...?”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jeanne Liedtka used a “waterline” graphic to discuss the potential impact of Design Thinking on people. Which of the following is true about the relationship between Design Thinking processes and people’s behaviors?",
    "answers": [
      "Behaviors related to Design Thinking can be observed, monitored, encouraged, and perhaps even measured."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a gift of Design Thinking?",
    "answers": ["Ability to stay in the question"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your volunteer group will meet next week to collaborate on an idea for a fundraising event. You realize that participants may have a broad range of perspectives and goals. You have been asked to facilitate the meeting. You plan to use a Design Thinking approach. Which of the following is an appropriate goal for your meeting?",
    "answers": ["Finding common ground"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Design Thinking, which of the following contributes most strongly to our success in moving from “Ideas to Action”?",
    "answers": ["Using data from experiments"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Design Thinking can help us to curate, similar to the role of a museum curator. Which of the following best describes this opportunity?",
    "answers": [
      "Drill down to the essence of an issue and see what really matters."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a strategic contribution of Design Thinking to teams and organizations?",
    "answers": ["Increase the speed of learning."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a strategic contribution of Design Thinking?",
    "answers": ["Leave space in the emergence of the solution."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team plans to use Design Thinking to tackle a complicated business problem. The team is working to define the problem challenge. Which of the following best expresses the relationship between a complex problem challenge and stakeholder mapping?",
    "answers": [
      "Stakeholder mapping is a way to identify relevant people and reduce the risk of our solutions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your manager sees the project team working on a stakeholder map. The manager wants to know if this is a reasonable use of their time. Which of the following best describes the purpose of stakeholder mapping?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify people and groups relevant to the opportunity and whose attitudes or behaviors can affect the success of our solution."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are introducing a colleague to the Design Thinking tool: stakeholder mapping. Which of the following is a benefit of stakeholder mapping?",
    "answers": ["Focus on creating value for others."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is eager to learn more about stakeholder mapping. A team member asks you how and when to use this tool during the Design Thinking process. Which of the following is your best reply?",
    "answers": [
      "Create a stakeholder map early in the Design Thinking process. Continue to revisit and refine the map throughout the process."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is preparing to work on a Design Thinking stakeholder map. They are not quite sure which people and groups should be included on the map. They ask your advice. Which of the following is a best practice?",
    "answers": ["When in doubt, choose on the side of creating a broader list."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team members have discovered that stakeholder mapping is helpful in their current Design Thinking challenge. They want to know if it can be used in other situations, too. Which of the following best describes the types of organization settings in which stakeholder mapping can be useful?",
    "answers": [
      "Multiple levels, from organization-level to more fine-grained projects"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has generated an initial list of stakeholders. Using the Design Thinking approach, which of the following is your next best step?",
    "answers": [
      "Understand the relationship between stakeholders and the issue."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is conducting a stakeholder mapping session. A team member asks if there is any relationship between empathy and stakeholder mapping. Which of the following best describes the relationship between empathy, stakeholder mapping, and the success of your eventual solution?",
    "answers": [
      "Empathy helps us identify the behavioral and attitudinal considerations for each stakeholder that are necessary for our solution to be effective."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is taking a coffee break – and discussing stakeholders. They wonder what is driving stakeholder behavior. Which of the following is a best practice when considering stakeholders’ motivations?",
    "answers": ["Frame motivations in a positive light."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have identified and met with a variety of potential stakeholders for your current Design Thinking challenge. One thing is clear from your meetings: The stakeholders can’t even agree on the definition of the problem! How could you use stakeholder mapping to help you move forward?",
    "answers": [
      "Create an initial stakeholder map to identify each of the individuals and groups involved, as a first step towards collaborative dialogue."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team member asks you to describe Design Thinking personas. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "Fictional characters based on data from our ethnographic research"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has been examining their ethnographic research data. Themes and patterns are beginning to emerge! The happy team wants to know what to do next. You suggest that they use the persona tool. Why?",
    "answers": ["Uncover unarticulated needs."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are talking with a friend about your Design Thinking challenge. You explain that your team is developing personas. The friend says that it sounds like fun but wonders if it is also useful. Which of the following is your best answer to explain the power of personas?",
    "answers": [
      "Enhance our ability to build empathy with the people we wish to serve."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is ready to develop personas. They want to know how to begin. Which of the following is a recommended first step?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify a number of dimensions that seem to reveal important differences across interviewees."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has spent time with the ethnographic research results, identifying themes and similarities. They have also identified several useful differences. Exciting! What is the team’s next best step?",
    "answers": ["Play with various combinations of the differences."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is ready to begin identifying the dimensions that will help them develop personas. You explain that the team can work with various formats – and that you recommend the “two by two” matrix (2x2 chart drawn with two axes to create four quadrants). Why?",
    "answers": [
      "It gives the team a straightforward method and a manageable number to work with."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has created many two-by-two persona matrices (2x2 matrixes). Team members have placed sticky notes in quadrants of the various matrices. The sticky notes represent each of the people they’ve interviewed. The notes are placed in whatever quadrants seem appropriate. Now the team feels ready to choose one or more persona matrices to move forward with. Which of the following is your best-practice recommendation for selection?",
    "answers": [
      "Select the matrices that have sticky notes in at least three of the four quadrants."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are telling your neighbor about the use of personas in Design Thinking. Which of the following is a goal of generating personas?",
    "answers": ["Create more innovative ideas."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team have identified the personas that you wish to explore. You suggest that the team work together to map the journey of each persona. Which of the following is the most compelling reason to perform this task?",
    "answers": ["Identify the low points in each persona’s journey."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has decided to use the “two by two” (2x2) format to create persona matrices. Which of the following best describes the role (purpose) of the two axes in a 2x2 persona matrix?",
    "answers": ["Discern between observed behavioral habits."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team are using Design Thinking to reinvent the product delivery experience for customers. Today you will introduce the team to a powerful Design Thinking tool: the journey map. Which of the following best describes the purpose of a customer journey map?",
    "answers": ["Understand the current reality of the customer."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are explaining the Design Thinking process to your family. They are particularly intrigued by the journey map tool. They want to know how a map could possibly help you create a new solution. Why are journey maps important to the Design Thinking process?",
    "answers": ["Build empathy for our users and identify unmet needs."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team are getting ready to create a customer journey map. It is the team’s first experience with creating a map! A team member asks you the difference between a Design Thinking journey map and a traditional business process map (a flow diagram with boxes and connectors). Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "A customer journey map includes the parts of the customer’s journey that we can’t see."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are showing your Design Thinking journey map to a friend. Which of the following best describes a key characteristic of the journey’s “moments of truth”?",
    "answers": ["Emotional"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team has developed their first Design Thinking journey map. The map traces the journey of a potential new customer. You are ready to work with the team to identify key takeaways (learnings) from the map. Which of the following is typically a takeaway of journey mapping?",
    "answers": ["Blueprint for what’s happening with the customer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team wants to create a Design Thinking journey map of a potential customer. The team will show the map to organizational executives and managers. Which of these is a recommended journey map format?",
    "answers": [
      "A big visual showing the journey in time, from beginning to end (left to right)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have identified your problem challenge: improve the buyer’s experience during an online purchase from your store. You decide to create a customer journey map. Which of these is your best, first task?",
    "answers": ["Select the people whose experience you want to understand."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team plans to conduct ethnographic interviews with students who are deciding next steps in their education. The team will then use the interview findings to create journey maps. Knowing this, which of the following is a best practice during the actual interviews?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask questions about topics that are larger than the journey itself."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is in the “What Is” stage of the Design Thinking process. They interviewed more than a dozen potential users. Then they created an initial journey map for each user. The team enthusiastically asks you what you recommend next. Which of the following is a next, best step?",
    "answers": ["Look for themes."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is creating a customer journey map. As they map the steps, you encourage them also to include information about the various people, objects, and places that are part of the customer’s journey. Which of the following is the best reason for this recommendation?",
    "answers": [
      "Begin to build the initial framework of what the customer’s experience looks like."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are introducing value chain analysis to your team. You explain that value chain analysis can be considered the “organizational perspective” version of a different Design Thinking tool. Which tool is it?",
    "answers": ["Journey map"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A senior director has invited you to a meeting to discuss the organizational challenge that you and your team are tackling using Design Thinking. The director asks you to describe value chain analysis as used in Design Thinking. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "The study of an organization’s interaction with partners to produce, market, distribute, and support its offerings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is getting ready to tackle a new organizational challenge using the Design Thinking process. When is the first, best time to conduct an end-to-end value chain analysis?",
    "answers": ["During the exploration phase"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is eager to focus on innovation possibilities – and you introduce value chain analysis. This seems like a waste of time to them. They could be creating solutions! A team member yawns and asks you to explain the benefit of value chain analysis. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps ensure that our solution will be sustainable for the organization in the long term."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team are ready to draw the value chain for your organization. What is your first best step?",
    "answers": ["Work backwards from the end user."]
  },
  {
    "question": "An executive in your organization is interested in learning more about the Design Thinking tool: value chain analysis. The executive asks you what types of opportunities are appropriate for value chain analysis. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "Multiple levels, from specific opportunities to broader situations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team are at the point in the Design Thinking process where you are ready to start generating ideas. You suggest that the team first take time to revisit the value chain analysis that they created earlier. Why?",
    "answers": [
      "Spot inefficiencies that are ripe for rearrangement, perhaps by shifting boundaries in the chain."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is drawing your organization’s existing value chain. As the team works, you suggest that they also spend time analyzing and understanding the dynamics involved in the chain. Which of the following is a benefit of understanding these dynamics as you make your innovation decisions?",
    "answers": ["The ability to determine where to place innovation resources"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As Jeanne Liedtka explains in our video, the learning that you gain from value chain analysis can support your work as a leader. You can use value chain analysis to help you gain strategic new insights into your own innovation challenges and opportunities. She recommends three categories to help you translate value chain analysis findings into your personal action plan. What are the three categories?",
    "answers": ["Keep, lose, create"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Another Design Thinking team has requested your expertise! They are tackling a challenge related to new product development. Their team is constructing a value chain for this innovation challenge. The team knows that they should include a fundamental value proposition in their value chain drawing – but they are not sure whose perspective it should represent. Which of the following is your best answer?",
    "answers": ["The customer who will use the product"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sarah is designing a new product for a clothing company, and she is planning to hold a sensemaking discussion with her team. While she is holding the session, she wants to make sure their process addresses the right audience. What should be her and her team's target audience for their product?",
    "answers": [
      "The outliers at the extreme ends of the curve whose needs may be radically different from the norm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Edmi has a revolutionary idea that she believes will help improve the speed at which clinics can operate, leaving people sitting in the wait room less, getting what they need, and leaving satisfied from their visit. Instead of going through the key process of sensemaking alone, she plans to involve a team of other people. Why is this important?",
    "answers": [
      "She can uncover new insights and dig deeper than one ever could have individually."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Martin is busy working on a solution for a beverage company, and he is approaching the sensemaking phase of design thinking. He has noticed while working on previous projects that sensemaking can change innovators and their mindsets. Why is that?",
    "answers": [
      "They are comfortable with ambiguity to discover deeper meanings."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jonah is working on a branding project for a skincare company. He arranges a meeting of stakeholders to view his team's designs in order to get their approval and alignment. A member of his team asks him why alignment is needed before moving forward. Why is alignment so important?",
    "answers": [
      "It allows everyone to explore each others' views and be open to the idea that their own perspective may be missing something."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "John is the CEO for his firm and wants to lead an alignment session as part of a new initiative the firm is working on. He holds the meeting and is hesitant that any good will come from inviting a broad group of voices into the conversation, so he keeps the size small. Did he do something wrong?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes, he attempted to over-control access and interaction with this meeting by limiting the group size."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Teddy is attempting a new effective dialogue technique for his team. He connects his whole organization in dialogue in a retreat format. What term refers to this style of effective dialogue?",
    "answers": ["Future Search"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Adam is a project lead working for an auto parts company. He has formed a group, and is striving to achieve alignment for an upcoming project that he would like to implement. What is a critical FIRST step for him that cannot be overlooked?",
    "answers": [
      "Understanding and aligning on the definition of the problem and the needs for whom they are designing for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tom is looking to expand his knowledge on design thinking practices and looking to add more to his playbook. He finds a few articles on the practice of perspective taking and begins to read them. He sees the importance of perspective taking, and plans to add it to his practice. Which of the following best describes perspective taking?",
    "answers": [
      "Understanding and acknowledging others' perspectives while sharing your own in a meaningful way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes perspective making?",
    "answers": [
      "A group activity that requires people to come together, not only to understand each other, but to forge something collectively new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ned wants to create an environment for his team to practice design thinking and alignment without making anyone feel uncomfortable. He writes out why dialogue and the emphasis on dialogue is important in these meetings in order to get alignment. Which of these is NOT an emphasis of dialogue?",
    "answers": ["creating a formal process through negotiation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your team is implementing design thinking for the first time. What intrateam dynamic would you NOT expect to result from the DT process?",
    "answers": [
      "Increased employee empowerment resulting from clearly defined responsibilities assigned to each team member"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A member of your design team suggested a promising idea at the beginning of your project. With time, however, the idea became less feasible. Despite the rest of the team being ready to move on and test a new hypothesis, the original team member struggles to let go of their initial idea. This is an example of:",
    "answers": ["A Category 3 bias"]
  },
  {
    "question": "John has joined a team that is developing a branding solution for a client, and he wants to use this opportunity to become a better designer and innovator. At what point has John experienced the culmination of DT methodology?",
    "answers": [
      "Only once he becomes so accustomed to using the tools above that he becomes immersed in understanding his stakeholders' experience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Danny wants to use DT to gain a better understanding of his stakeholders. His team is new to the DT process. What should he do to help make his team more comfortable with DT's new way of thinking?",
    "answers": [
      "Help his team feel safe by outlining a structured and facilitated creative process for them to follow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following problems would NOT be best-served by hypothesis-driven thinking?",
    "answers": ["Creating financial projections for the upcoming year"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best example of the experience of immersion?",
    "answers": [
      "A public health official is looking to design a better outreach program for her city. She tours local hospitals, holds open discussions with concerned citizens, and gains a new perspective and appreciation for the struggles of the community.",
      "A mayor looking to design programs to better meet the needs of his city’s homeless population. He visits soup kitchens for food, tours shelter facilities, and gains a new perspective and appreciation for the struggles of the homeless population."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true when it comes to experiencing immersion?",
    "answers": ["Our biases can blind us"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jessica is the manager of a product design team. As she conducts her research and investigation, she knows she needs to be wary of several natural human tendencies to achieve true immersion. Which of the following would be an example of these negative tendencies?",
    "answers": [
      "During an end-user interview, the interviewee says something about the product that Jessica finds completely ridiculous. She decides to dismiss the idea and moves the conversation in a different direction."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following should Jill be sure to do during the design thinking process?",
    "answers": [
      "Look for extreme users to help figure out what future is already happening"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maggie is great at cognitive empathy, but struggles with affective empathy. Which of the following is Maggie likely to be good at handling?",
    "answers": [
      "Maggie is tasked with preparing for a negotiation where it will be important to understand her opponent's way of thinking."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The purpose of diversity in the Emergence stage is to...",
    "answers": [
      "identify new and better concepts that are superior to what any individual stakeholder could have brought into the conversation."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the process of presencing?",
    "answers": [
      "letting go of biases, assumptions and, ownership of ideas so we can “let come” new concepts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The process of selecting the least worst solution to which everyone will agree is called...",
    "answers": ["satisficing."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The heart of the Imagining phase involves...",
    "answers": ["visualization."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The story of the Australian company who used 10 separate “neighborhoods” to represent the 10 different departments is an example of which visualization tool?",
    "answers": ["metaphor"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does giving groups a lit-up light bulb (a symbol for the “Aha!” moment) yield greater creative output than those who did not receive such a stimulus?",
    "answers": [
      "Visual metaphors create a shortcut around normal language processes that aim straight for how we think and feel."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Instead of viewing prototypes as “dress rehearsals” for a finished product, we should view them as...",
    "answers": ["provocations to engage others in rich conversation."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Describing a baby as “a ten pound bundle of joy with a smile as bright as the sun” is an example of...",
    "answers": ["metaphor."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sketching within the Imagining phase can be a powerful medium to...",
    "answers": ["communicate ideas both visually and verbally."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In traditional R&D, we produce the “thing” as it is supposed to be, and then test. In the Imagining phase of DT, on the other hand, what do we do?",
    "answers": [
      "use the “thing” as a vehicle to a better conversation and to get better feedback"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the purpose of the Design Thinking tool: job to be done (JTBD)?",
    "answers": ["Uncover and document the desired outcome of the user."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have explained to the team that the job to be done tool is a critical piece of your innovation project. A team member asks why. Which of these is your best response?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps focus our work on what the user is trying to accomplish, and it may reframe the project."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The job to be done tool has two components. One component is “emotional.” What is the other component?",
    "answers": ["Functional"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the emotional component of the Design Thinking tool: job to be done?",
    "answers": [
      "It is essential to our solution’s success but difficult for users to articulate."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and a colleague are getting ready to conduct an ethnographic interview. You recommend creating an ethnographic interview guide (sometimes called a discussion guide). Your colleague asks you to describe the purpose of a guide. Which of the following is your best response?",
    "answers": ["A plan for the interview, including topics and fail-safe"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your colleague are planning to conduct an ethnographic interview with a potential user. You have chosen your interview roles. Your colleague will be notetaker. You will be interviewer. As interviewer, which of the following is your best approach during the main questions portion of the interview?",
    "answers": ["Open-ended questions and perhaps an empathy-building activity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As shown in our videos, the Kingwood design team applied Design Thinking throughout their work. Which of the following best describes their approach to initial research?",
    "answers": [
      "Devote time to deep discovery and to the development of empathy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As shown in our Kingwood story, an important element of Design Thinking is our ability to define the problem. Which of the following does our Kingwood story best illustrate?",
    "answers": [
      "Successful design begins with the nature of the questions that we ask."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your design team has invited stakeholders to a workshop. Your workshop goal: Imagine an ideal, shared garden space. To prepare, your team set up a patch of (fake) grass. They created cards and stickers showing possible garden elements and activities. (They also left a few blank cards and stickers for participants’ ideas.) During the workshop, you will ask participants to place the cards and stickers in areas of preference on the grass. You hope to get an idea of what could be popular in the final garden space. Which Design Thinking technique does this best describe?",
    "answers": ["Co-creation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You and your team want to use Design Thinking to improve people’s lives through innovative solutions. You already know that tackling these challenges will take you into new, uncharted terrain. Which of the following is a typical characteristic of most of the people you wish to serve?",
    "answers": [
      "Most people will have limits on their ability to correctly articulate their needs."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes what Kathryn Schultz calls \"investigative doubt?\"",
    "answers": [
      "the attitude of doubt fueled by curiosity rather than cynicism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best exemplifies the mindset of a designer?",
    "answers": ["Antonio's work lends itself more to invention than discovery."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Esther is the lead designer on a project for a manufacturer of medical supplies, and her team has a solution in mind. Her teammates suggests that they should try for a better solution by taking a different approach, but Esther is hesitant to abandon what they already have. Of which Category 3 bias is this situation an example?",
    "answers": ["the Endowment Effect"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Steve is a member of a team of designers working on a branding project for a Fortune 500 company. He has enjoyed the process overall, but early on he found himself a little overwhelmed by the pace of changes that occured as the team prepared to test their prototypes with consumers. Once he changes some habits and reorients his focus to better fit the developments of the project, he is able to make some key contributions during the testing process. Which of following aspects of \"becoming\" related to learning in action best describes Steve's transformation?",
    "answers": ["He has become more adaptive"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's important that we test our hypotheses in an organized and thoughful manner as we drive toward innovative solutions. Which of the following steps should we NOT include in our hypothesis-driven testing process?",
    "answers": ["Begin with an amiguous problem"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerome is developing an inventory management solution with a team of designers. The development process had a bumpy start, but as they moved through testing their solutions with managers in the field, Jerome noticed that admitting some of his personal mistakes - which he found hard to do earlier - allowed him and his team to correct errors and improve their testing. Which of the following mindset shifts related to learning in action best describes his experience?",
    "answers": ["going from needing to be right to being willing to be wrong"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mark decided to forego real-world experimentation while designing a project for his client. He conducted many user interviews during the design process, but there are a number of error reports coming in during the initial deployment of the solution. Which of the following common error points is Mark most likely encountering?",
    "answers": ["addressing insights inadequately in solutions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Greg is working on a product design for a lawncare company, and they are currently conducting testing. Throughout the process, he is constantly fixating on small details and noting minor imperfections with experiments. This is making it hard to move forward, and his teammates are becoming frustated with the process. Which of the following difficult aspects of learning in action best describes Greg's situation?",
    "answers": ["He's seeking perfection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Natasha is working toward experimentation on a road safety solution. She thinks back on specific times from her past in which she worked on public safety projects, and makes notes about how they might apply to her current project. To which of the following steps from David Kolb's learning model does this action most closely apply?",
    "answers": ["concrete experience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Claudia is designing an interface for an online shopping app with her team. They feel like they have gathered some strong ideas and gotten off to a good start, but they now want to build on their ideas and observations to create meaning and purpose within their design process that is both personal and shared. In which of the phases discussed in this course is Claudia's group currently working?",
    "answers": ["Sensemaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What has research shown us to be the least utilized Design Thinking tool?",
    "answers": ["surfacing assumptions behind ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best exemplifies the mindset of a scientist?",
    "answers": ["Anna's work lends itself more to discovery than invention."]
  },
  {
    "question": "David is the lead designer on a project for a prominent car manufacturer. One of the members of his team has brought him an idea that the others seem very excited about. David has a hard time envisioning the idea, so he tells the team he's going to go with a more familiar approach. Of which Category 3 bias is this situation an example?",
    "answers": ["the Availability Bias"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carolyn is a member of a team of designers working on a branding project for a Fortune 500 company. The stress of the project has been intense, and after a few mistakes early on Carolyn wasn't sure if she would be able to remain on the team. But during testing, she really focuses and is able to use her learning from experiments to iterate some exciting solutions. This has given her the sense that she can recover from mistakes and make valuable contributions. Which of the following aspects of \"becoming\" related to learning in action best describes Carolyn's transformation?",
    "answers": ["She has become more resilient"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's important that we test our hypotheses in an organized and thoughful manner as we drive toward innovative solutions. Which of the following steps should we include in our hypothesis-driven testing process?",
    "answers": ["Define the problem"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anita is developing a customer feedback solution with a team of designers. The development process slowed nearly to a halt as they began testing, but things improved once Anita realized she had been too quick to dismiss ideas as \"bad\" instead of seeking out information that might prove her wrong. Which of the following mindset shifts related to learning in action best describes her experience?",
    "answers": [
      "moving from passing judgment to adopting investigative doubt that seeks out disconfirming data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Amy is designing a prototype for a mobile app interface. She has conducted real-world experiments with a large group and gathered detailed feedback from potential consumers, but when she reveals an updated prototype to her project lead, the project lead says it seems like much of the most valuable feedback from testing isn't reflected in the update. Which of the following common error points is Amy most likely encountering?",
    "answers": ["addressing insights inadequately in our solutions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eric is working on a water filtration system. He and his team are finally getting out in the field to test their system with a group of customers, and they're ready to carefully record the results. To which of the following steps from David Kolb's learning model does this most closely apply?",
    "answers": ["active experimentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Claudia is designing an interface for an online shopping app with her design team. They have some ideas to work with, but they have just begun the project and feel as though they are just beginning their design journey. In which of the phases discussed in this course is Claudia's group currently working?",
    "answers": ["Immersion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mary has just completed design thinking training and is ready to use what she learned on a new work project. What is an example of an impact she might expect to see on a personal level?",
    "answers": [
      "An increased sense of creative confidence and psychological safety"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "John has joined a team that is developing a branding solution for a client, and he wants to use this opportunity to become a better designer and innovator. Which of the following should be John's chief focus during the design thinking process?",
    "answers": ["Immersing himself in the users' lives"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Danny wants to use DT to gain a better understanding of his stakeholders. Which of the following should he prioritize last according to DT core practices?",
    "answers": [
      "Using surveys to gather quantitative data on customer behavior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria is a project manager working on a branding campaign for an electronics company, and she wants to improve her design thinking process. She feels that in the past she has focused too much on her own view of what works, and wants to become more open to the ideas and concerns of both her coworkers and her target audience. To achieve this growth, which of the following mindset shifts would she want to avoid undertaking?",
    "answers": ["Going from empathetic to egocentric"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following DOES NOT aid our capacity to understand the needs of others?",
    "answers": ["The part of the limbic system that triggers fear"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Breanna has an idea she's very excited about. She believes this idea could help improve the speed at which clinics can operate, leaving people sitting in the wait room less, getting what they need, and leaving satisfied from their visit. Instead of going through the key process of sensemaking on her own, she plans to involve a team of other people. Why is this important?",
    "answers": [
      "She can uncover new insights and dig deeper than one ever could have individually."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "John is approaching the sensemaking phase of Design Thinking. He has noticed in the past that sensemaking can change innovators and their mindsets. Why is that?",
    "answers": [
      "They are comfortable with ambiguity to discover deeper meanings."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is alignment so important?",
    "answers": [
      "It allows everyone to explore each others' views and be open to the idea that their own view may be missing something."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Clare is designing a new product for a clothing company, and she is planning to hold a sensemaking discussion with her team. When she is holding the session, who should her and her team's focus be for the target audience of their potential product?",
    "answers": [
      "The people in the middle of the bell curve and the outliers at each extreme"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kate is a senior leader in her firm and is planning to lead an alignment session. She invites her organization (about 45 people) to an alignment session to bring about inclusiveness and make sure all ideas are heard and taken note of when coming to an alignment. She does not attend the meeting as she has other conflicts, but is confident her team will produce a good result. What is the most important thing that Kate missed when setting up this meeting?",
    "answers": [
      "Kate included way too many people to be productive and get the desired results from alignment."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The goal of the Emergence stage is to...",
    "answers": [
      "help shift innovators from a state of individualized, isolated problem-solving to a collective state of possibility-thinking."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The idea that to adapt successfully to the diversity of challenges in our environment, we must (as a whole) have the same level of diversity represented in our experiences most accurately describes which of the following?",
    "answers": ["law of requisite variety"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Leaving room for others to create what COULD BE instead of being told what WILL BE is an example of the power of...",
    "answers": ["emptiness."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stories, sketches, paper prototypes, and journey maps are all types of...",
    "answers": ["visualization tools."]
  },
  {
    "question": "75% of our brain’s sensory neurons are dedicated to...",
    "answers": ["processing visuals."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The most productive strategy when pairing business leaders and designers together in teams suggests that...",
    "answers": [
      "business leaders should attempt to engage in visualization techniques alongside designers."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A member of your team recently went through a crisis in their personal life. You notice they are dismissive of almost every idea your team suggests, despite having supported several of them just a week before. This is an example of which type of bias?",
    "answers": ["Hot/Cold Gap"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jessica is the leader of a project design team. As she conducts her research and investigation, she knows she needs to be wary of several natural human tendencies to achieve true immersion. Which of the following would NOT be an example of these tendencies?",
    "answers": [
      "Jessica is unsure where her research will ultimately take her but is curious about the end-user perspective on her product. She confidently walks up to strangers and talks to them about their experience with her product."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maggie is great at affective empathy, but struggles with cognitive empathy. Which of the following is Maggie likely to be good at handling?",
    "answers": [
      "Maggie gets a call from her best friend Bonnie whose dog just died. Bonnie asks her to come over because she needs a friend."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eliza is attempting a new effective dialogue technique for her team. She creates dialogue around the positive elements of an issue and involves asking questions that improve the capability to reach its positive potential. What term refers to this style of effective dialogue?",
    "answers": ["Appreciative Inquiry"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes perspective taking?",
    "answers": [
      "Understanding and acknowledging others' perspectives while sharing your own in a meaningful way."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Michelle wants to create an environment for his team to practice design thinking and alignment without making anyone feel uncomfortable. She writes out why dialogue and the emphasis on dialogue is important in these meetings in order to get alignment. Which of these is NOT an emphasis of dialogue?",
    "answers": ["creating a formal process through negotiation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following should Jill avoid doing during the design thinking process?",
    "answers": ["Using data from the past to predict the future"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Heather is a project lead working for a sporting goods company. She has formed a group, and is striving to achieve alignment for an upcoming project. What is a critical FIRST step for her that cannot be overlooked?",
    "answers": [
      "Understanding and aligning on the definition of the problem and the needs for whom they are designing for"
    ]
  }
]
